晚上 7：15
竞选之夜
东海岸投票马上就要结束了 夫人
East Coast polls are closing, ma'am.
夫人
Ma'am...
历史正在召唤您 您得亲自应答
History is calling, and it won't go to voicemail.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗 夫人?
You okay, ma'am?
我想喝点东西 Gary 谢谢
Oh, I'd love one, Gary. Thank you.
好吧 我 我去给您拿来
Okay, I'll get... I'll get you one.
我询问美国是否愿意让我当她的总统
Well, I've asked America if she wants me to be her president.
现在她该给我们一个答案了
Now she's gonna give us her answer.
夫人 美国不仅仅爱着你
America doesn't just love you, ma'am,
她只为你钟情
she is in love with you.
我们失去了肯塔基州的支持!
We've lost Kentucky!
那么 我想你已经接触过O'Brien的团队了
So I assume you reached out to the O'Brien camp.
你和谁谈过 Charlotte还是Kim?
Taking a meeting with Charlotte or with Kim?
不 我没联系过他们
No, I haven't contacted the O'Brien team.
Amy 如果他赢了 我们的行情就会像
Amy, if he wins, our lobbying
黑猩猩的咪咪下垂的一样厉害
stock is gonna droop like a chimp's tits.
我们就不再是炙手可热的干将了
We're not gonna be the golden kids anymore.
我们要让他留意到我们的价值
We've got to stay on his radar.
但我们也得跟随她啊
But we need to be in with her, too.
- 她也有可能获胜 - 是啊
- She might win. - Yeah.
明面上 我会跟她站在同一战线
Well, on air I'm gonna keep in with her.
下了节目 我就会把她给卖了
Off air I'm telling the Nazis that she's hiding in the attic.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嗨 - 嗨 那么...
- Hi. - Hey, so...
当然 我们请到了Sally Davenport
we have Sally Davenport with us, of course.
还有Matty Curtis
We've also got Matty Curtis.
- 哇 - 爱死那个家伙了
- Wow. - Love that guy.
那个网上的数据统计专家
The online statistics savant.
是啊 在中期选举时
Yeah, in the midterms,
每个参议院席位的胜率他都预测到了
he predicted the margin in every Senate seat.
受死吧 福克斯(福克斯台有自己的数据统计,一向偏共和党)
So, suck it, Fox.
我们现在是要开始还是怎样?
So we doing this or what?
谢天谢地你来啦
Hey, well, thank God you're here.
没人知道今晚局势会如何  玩得开心
No one else here knows how tonight will go. Have fun.
- 期待看到你的表现 - 好的
- Yeah, we'll see you out there. - Okay.
这是我印象里竞争最激烈的一次选举了
So, closest election in living memory.
- 对啊 - 希望你们做好准备了
- Yeah. - Hope you guys are prepared.
- 我们会做到最好 - 我希望你们能做的比最好还要好
- We will do our best. - Well, we're gonna need better than that.
- 没问题 - 开个玩笑 开个玩笑罢了
- Okay. - I'm kidding. I'm just kidding.
但你们最好能表现好
But you better be good.
不好意思 我们要清场了
Sorry, guys, we need this area to be clear.
Meyer-James团队 巴尔的摩
等下 你是那个蛋蛋兄
Hey, wait, it's the testicle man.
罪名成立 仔细核实 请勿忽视
Guilty as charged. Check 'em, don't neglect 'em.
那个蛋蛋事件对你来说确实帮了大忙啊 先生
This whole scrotum situation is really working out for you, sir.
那个听证会简直糟透了
That hearing was terrible,
但我确实因此红了 你知道吗?
but it really got my face out there, you know?
你现在是办公室受欺凌方和生殖健康的代表
You're the face of workplace bullying and genital health.
看看这个 Mike让我去总统套间
Look at this. Mike wants me up in the presidential suite
他说总统想当面 单独感谢我
to get a one-on-one thank-you from the president.
- 我看起来怎么样? - 很棒
- How do I look? - Great.
谢谢
Thanks.
不 不 不 不 是单独哦
Oh, no, no, no. One-on-one.
哦 对 好吧
Oh, yeah, okay.
老天 选举之夜简直让我上瘾
Oh, man, election nights are my cocaine.
曾经选举之夜和可卡因都让我上瘾 但是...
It used to be election nights and cocaine were my cocaine, but...
如果Fox台说票数很接近 那就一定是这样
If Fox says it's close, then it must be.
- 还有 他们说庆祝时刻也即将到来 - 有消息了吗?
- Then again, they said the Rapture was close. - Anything yet?
印第安纳州和南卡罗莱纳支持O'Brien(共20票)
Indiana and South Carolina, they just called for O'Brien.
佛蒙特州和康涅狄克州支持我们(共10票)
Uh, Vermont and Connecticut, yep, they're for us.
耶 佛蒙特州! 耶 康涅狄克州!
Yeah, Vermont! Yeah, Connecticut!
好了 淡定 这两个州算个毛
Okay, settle down. A bowl of hair could win those states.
- 夫人 您有时间见Jonah吗? - 对 Jonah 有的
- Ma'am, you have a moment for Jonah? - Oh, Jonah. Oh, yeah.
我对你在男性健康上的贡献以及 开诚布公的
I want to thank you for your work on men's health
讲述你在工作中所忍受的欺凌 表示衷心的感谢
and talking about that bullying that you had to endure.
谢谢你 夫人 这是我的荣幸
Thank you, ma'am. It was my honor...
知道吗? 我还要感谢佛蒙特州
You know what? I need to thank Vermont.
就到这吧 Jonah 今夜是个忙碌之夜
Yeah, that's it, Jonah. It's been a busy night.
这算什么? 她只腾出大概四秒钟的时间给我
What was that? I got, like, four seconds.
其他人只有两秒钟呢 别逼逼了
Well, most people get just two.
威斯康星州投票结果的预测 夫人
Projections for Wisconsin, ma'am.
- 很好 - 我还没有看过
- Great. - I haven't read them yet.
我会留着这些 等进了监狱再读
I'm saving that for when I go to prison.
50%几率上电椅
Even money they give you the chair.
没有人安然无恙的从听证会出来 Bill
No one came out of the hearings unscathed, Bill.
我不得不背弃我的未婚夫
I had to ditch my fiancé.
当我和我的监狱未婚夫在一起的时候
I'll be thinking about that while I'm with whichever guy
- 我会想起你的话的 – 恶
- makes me his prison fiancé. - Ew.
Gary 我今晚邀请了一个朋友过来陪着我
Oh, Gary, I asked a friend to come and be with me tonight.
- 多好啊 – 是Karen
- How nice. - Yeah, Karen.
- 卧槽! - 什么
- Fuck! - What?
抽筋了
Cramp.
根据我们的预测 O'Brien有33张选举人票
Senator O'Brien has 33 electoral votes based on our projection.
Meyer总统有10张 你觉得是否胜负已分 Dan?
President Meyer has 10. Is this significant, Dan?
美国大选夜 CNN预测
我觉得现在下结论还为时尚早
Oh, I think it's far, far too early to tell at this point.
CNN 总统前任竞选顾问
- 我是说大选真的是... - 非常明显了
- I mean the election really... - Very significant.
摇摆州选票的不确定性已经渗入到其他地区
Uncertainty in battleground states is bleeding into other areas.
人数较少的众州将会左右此次竞选结果
It's the suburbs that are gonna decide this contest.
Amy Dan 在你们看来 谁将在今晚的竞选中获胜?
Well, Amy, Dan, who do you feel will win tonight?
- 都有可能 - 都有可能
- It's so close. - So close.
此时此刻真说不出来
It's a tough call to make at this point.
不仅我们如此 对全美民众而言也是如此
Mm-hmm, and not just for us, Greg, but for America.
真是鬼斧神工的胡说八道
That was transcendent bullshitting.
好吧 我这么跟你说吧
Well, I'll tell you one thing,
就算我真的输了 我也会输的像赢家一样精彩
if I do lose, I'm gonna lose like a winner.
- 你不会输的 好吗? - 没错 没错
- You're not gonna lose, okay? - Right. Right.
你会赢得一帆风顺
You're gonna win in a slide.
虽然 顺的有点艰难
You know, marginally.
哇哦 看看谁来了!
Oh, my God, look who's here!
- 嗨 是Karen哦 - 是Karen
- Hi, it's Karen. - It's Karen.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 大家看 Karen来了 - 噢 嗨 Tom
- Everybody, Karen. - Oh, hi, Tom.
我是Karen 对 我们在会上见过
Karen. Yeah, we met at the convention.
不理我 好吧
Okay.
告诉我最近过的怎样
Tell me how you're doing.
呃 我尝试着保持乐观
Well, I'm trying to stay positive.
俄克拉荷马州"失陷"了
We lost Oklahoma.
本来我们很有把握的 所以...
Which we were expected to, so...
不过只有七票罢了
It's only seven votes.
- 啊! 该死的毛毯
-  Ah! These damn hotel carpets.
一直给我打静电
I keep getting that static electric shock.
- 你需要一个
- You need one of those
离子手镯把静电导走 - 好主意
ionic bracelets that grounds you. - Good call.
我一直都想不透怎么在监狱上厕所
It's the prison toilet situation which preys on one's mind.
在别人的密切注视下大便  难以想象
Defecating in full view of another man is unthinkable.
抱歉 Bill 但我一点也不想讨论这个话题
Forgive me, Bill, but I don't wish to ever discuss this.
没错 Bill 那塞子塞上吧 行吗?
Yeah, Bill, put a cork in it, will you?
其实 说不定有用呢
You know, that actually may help.
嘿 问你件事 你付了多少钱给你的律师?
Hey, listen, how much did you pay your lawyers?
因为我找了律师参加听证会
Because I lawyered up for the hearings
结果他们居然收了我15000美元
and they charged me 15 grand
他们只不过是说了几个词而已 是吧?
and they only said words, you know?
嘘! 有电话来了
Shh! There's a call coming.
他就像个印第安追踪者
He's like a Native American tracker.
能听风预警
He can hear it in the wind.
预计参议员O'Brien会赢得
Senator O'Brien is the predicted victor
- 明尼苏达州的投票(10票) - 啊 操!
- in the great state of Minnesota. - Oh, fuck!
- 我以为那州会是我们的 - 我以为已经是我们的了
- I thought that was ours. - I thought we had it.
- 我不确定 - 夫人
- I wasn't entirely sure. - Ma'am.
- 靠 - 耽搁您几分钟
- Shit. - Excuse me for one second.
我不是说我们会 因为我们不会
I'm not saying we will, because we won't,
但是万一真的我们输了 而你就要卸任了 你能...
but if we do lose and you're an outgoing president, you could...
-我会赦免你? - 嗯
- I could pardon you? - Yes.
如果真那样可不太好 你会是第一个这么说的人
That wouldn't look good. You'd be the first person to say that.
我不确定在这种情况下我会是第一个
I'm not entirely sure I would in this circumstance.
- 如果有什么方法... -嘿 Bill 还有很多电话等着
- If there's any way... - Hey, Bill, I got a lot on the line
我这个现任总统去处理
with my presidency right now,
所以我真的没有时间
so I don't really have time to
来考虑你说的那些狗屁东西
be thinking about your whatever the fuck it is.
- 可能到来的牢狱之灾 - 没错
- Probable imprisonment. - Exactly.
- 谢谢您 夫人 - 不用谢
- Thank you, ma'am. - You're welcome.
白宫西翼办公室
如果是O'Brien赢了你会怎么办?
What will you do if O'Brien wins?
和Selina一起办公室搬到贝蒂福特戒断康复中心?
Set up an office with Selina at the Betty Ford Clinic?
不 我会另谋差事的
No, I've applied for a job outside.
政治把我烦的不轻
Politics bores me.
可以说是烦了个彻彻底底明明白白真真切切
It bores the living hell out of me.
天啊 真是烦得很
God, it's boring.
Amy不在状态  走神了
Amy looks off her game, distracted.
Amy给我唯一的印象就是东奔西跑
I only really know Amy as the woman who rushed everywhere
紧攥着电话 不知道的还以为攥着的是她的冷冻胚胎呢
clutching her phone like it contained her frozen embryos.
她是个工作狂
She's a workaholic.
拼命工作 来掩饰她
Works frantically to avoid dealing with her weird mix
缺乏自尊而又自恋的扭曲心理
of lack of self-worth and narcissism.
我很喜欢她
I really like her.
呃 夫人 我真心不想一出现就带来坏消息 但是...
Uh, ma'am, I don't mean to be the bearer of bad news, but...
威斯康星州来电 预计是O'Brien赢了
Called Wisconsin. Projected as an O'Brien win.
就是这个坏消息 终归不是我带来的了
That was the bad news, which in the end I didn't bear.
呃 这肯定出乎很多人的预料
Well, this is certainly something not many people saw coming.
在我看来 这就是多米诺骨牌效应 暗示着O'Brien今晚的胜利
For me, it's the domino that signals an O'Brien victory tonight.
对O'Brien来说这真是很大的 压倒性的胜利
This is a big, big win for O'Brien,
我想Meyer团队也会感受到的
and I think the Meyer team is gonna be feeling that.
压倒性胜利
The bigness.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
Amy这说明你的前上司已露败象了么?
Amy, is the race already slipping away from your former boss?
不 不
No. No.
呃 还有很多投票没有结束
Um, a lot of the polls have not closed yet.
Amy Brookheimer  CNN前Meyer竞选经纪人
所以 不 不 你懂的 我不这么认为
So, no. No, you know, it's no.
我觉得O'Brien会赢得选举
I think O'Brien's gonna win this election.
O'Brien不可能成为总统的
O'Brien can't be president.
他还得按合约继续当肯德基的商标呢
He's still contracted to be the KFC logo.
- 呃... - 你会赢的 夫人
- Eh... - You're gonna win this, ma'am.
- 我不知道 - 你会的
- I don't know. - You are.
- 你觉得你会赢吗? - 什么意思?
- You think you would have won? - What do you mean?
如果你是候选人 你觉得你会赢吗?
If you had been the candidate, you think you would have won?
- 那不过是投机的想法罢了 你知道的
-  'Cause that's the speculation, you know.
你觉得呢 Karen?
What do you think, Karen?
关于某件具体的事情 还是...?
About something specific, or...?
我和总统是否应该交换身份?
Should the president and I have swapped roles?
- 什么情景? - 选举
- For? - For the election.
这次选举 正在进行的这次选举
This election. There's an election going on.
噢 呃 你问我的是假设的问题
Oh, well, you're asking me a hypothetical question
我得好好的回答
and I need to answer it as best I can.
好吧 你刚刚已经做到了
Okay, well, you just did.
太棒了
Great.
Amy 我刚刚看到你在电视上情绪不太稳定
Amy, I saw your instability on TV.
收到后给我回电话
Call me when you get this.
如果你不方便的话就让别人替你打号
Get someone else to dial if you're in a straightjacket.
嘿 我在给O'Brien发一些我们这边的数据
Hey, I'm sending some of our data to O'Brien.
如果他赢了 我得去给他舔菊
If he wins this thing, I need to kiss his ass.
是啊 我闪了 我得离开
Mm-hmm. I'm going. I have to go.
什么? 你不能走
What? No, you can't do that.
我得陪着Selina等结果出来
Yeah, no, I have to see this play out with Selina.
我人生三分之一的时间都在为今晚做准备 所以
I've spent a third of my life leading up to this night, so...
Amy...
Greg 我得走了
Greg, I have to go.
- 你得走了? - 是的
- You have to go? - Yeah.
这是什么意思? 这又不是夏令营 任你来去
What does that mean? This is not summer camp.
我只是觉得另外一个地方更需要我
Well, I just feel that I'm needed elsewhere.
哦 好啊 那就请离开吧
Oh, well, then please go.
反正一些观众
Some of our viewers were
在抱怨你的声音太刺耳...
complaining that you're shrill anyway, so...
哦 刺耳? 不 不 我的声音从不刺耳
Oh, shrill? No, no, I'm never shrill.
那就是… 哦!
And that's... Oh!
你搞得像我的声音现在就很刺耳一样
And you're acting as though I'm sounding shrill right now?
好啊 继续保持暗示我声音很刺耳的表情吧
Yeah, yeah, keep making that face implying that I'm shrill.
喂 谁能去停车场看看
Hey, could someone check the parking lot?
我觉着所有的车子都在叫
I think all the alarms are going off.
很遗憾你失去了他
Sorry for your loss, ma'am.
我是指威斯康辛 不是指人
I mean about Wisconsin, not a person.
嗷! 操!
Ow! Fuck!
我忘了 我的鞋子和地毯气场不和（静电）
I forgot. I have incompatible shoes with the rug.
- 天啊 - 对不起
- God. - I'm so sorry.
关于Meyer总统 我们没多少好消息
We don't have a lot of good news for President Meyer.
去他妈的 这一晚就是
Screw this whole sloppy,
乱七八糟的后座吹箫之夜 老娘不管了
backseat blowjob of a night anyway. I don't give a shit.
- 等等 - 怎么了?
- Hang on. - Hang on what?
威斯康辛的结果被撤回了
The Wisconsin call has been rescinded.
你是说又回到待定状态了？
You mean they went back on the call?
是的 所以我说他们撤回了结果
Yes, hence my saying that they had.
撤回这个词其实不能让人马上理解
Rescinded is actually not a word that's immediately clear.
- 这简直是360度大逆转啊 - 是180度
- This is a 360-degree turn. -  It's 180.
撤回现在是我最喜欢的词!
Rescinded is my new favorite word!
我们又有戏唱了 死后复生
We are back in the game. Back from the dead.
僵尸们 决胜局开始了
Zombies, bottom of the ninth.
夫人 听着
Ma'am, listen to this.
福克斯台宣布科罗拉多是你的了(9票)
Fox just called Colorado for you.
- 不是吧 - 哦 天啊
- No! - Oh, my God!
都往后退 Meyer已经势不可挡了
Stand back, Meyer is on fire.
快看 妈妈 CNN也宣布了
Look, look. Mom, CNN has it, too.
看起来Matty的多明诺骨牌又站回原位了
It appears that Matty's domino is standing up straight again.
很显然这非常出人意料
Obviously this is a shock
- 需要仔细分析 - 是啊
- and needs some unpacking. - Mm-hmm.
哦 是啊 你是得好好分析分析
Oh, yeah, you better unpack it.
"来看看现在我们能不能分析这东西"
"Let's see if we can unpack this now."
"哦 我头上长了阴毛"
"Oh, I've got pubic hair on my head."
模型的准确性取决于你输入的数据
The models are only as good as the data that you put into them
而数据来自民意调查公司
and the data comes from the polling companies.
所以也许我们应该问问他们什么地方出问题了
So maybe we should talk to them about what went wrong.
- 你的网站就是一坨屎 - 真心是屎啊
- Your website is shit. - Honest to God. Shit.
- 就是屎 - 快回你的夏尔去吧
- It's shit. - Go back to the Shire,
- 你个圆脸的霍比特人 - 是啊
- you fucking moonfaced hobbit. - Yeah.
夫人 我们能单独聊聊吗?
You know, ma'am, can we talk privately?
哦 当然 好啊
Oh, sure, yeah.
我觉得我对这次竞选
I'd like to think that I have been
- 起到了一些作用 - 你做的很棒
- some use to the campaign. - You've been great.
我是说 所有人都说
I mean, you know, everyone's like,
"哦 Tom James 哦 那是Tom James
"Oh, Tom James. Ooh, it's Tom James.
他是我男神 在我的胸上签名吧  Tom James"
He's so dreamy. Sign my tits, Tom James."
呃 那么 你是想说?
Um, but anyway, so... But you were saying?
总统女士
Madam President,
我不想手中无权
I don't want to be impotent.
我 我不是…
I... I don't really...
- 在你领导的政府里 我不想手中无权 - 哦 对啊!
- In your administration. - Oh, right!
我以前和你一样 有过这样的谈话
I have had this very conversation.
你想第一个进入内阁会议 最后一个走
You want to be first in, last out of cabinet meetings.
- 你想... - 不 我想做财政部长
- You want... - No, I want to be treasury secretary.
- 什么? - 同时兼任副总统
- What? - As well as veep.
你想要我的财政大权?
You want to run my economy?
Tom James银行
Bank of Tom James.
- 我真的是极为失望... - 恕我直言...
- I am bitterly disappointed... - With respect...
- 你... - 恕我直言
- that you... - With respect,
这届政府在听证会的时候
this administration was coming apart at the seams
差点就分崩离析了 而我用了六大卷
during those hearings and I used six rolls
魔力胶布把它粘了起来
of Magic Tape to stick it back together.
你还想要什么吗?
Anything else you want to ask for?
需要把你的脸印在钞票上吗?
Want your face on money or something?
想要那个电视吗? 拿去吧
Want that TV? Take it.
...进入 布劳沃德县的投票率很低(弗罗里达大郡)
...coming in, a low voter turnout in Broward County.
今晚布劳沃德县的投票率很低(弗罗里达共占29-31票)
? It's a low turnout in Broward County tonight ?
今晚布劳沃德县的投票率很低
? Low turnout in Broward County tonight. ?
- 跟我一起唱 - 不
- Sing with me. - No.
你申请的是...是什么工作?
What's this... this job you've applied for?
是个大型食品公司 联合调味品公司
It's a big food corporation. United Seasonings.
他们供应了全国90%的辣椒粉
They supply 90% of the country's paprika.
是的 我们帮他们游说过
Yep, we lobbied for them,
所以我的手被辣椒粉公司的钱弄脏了
so my hands are dirty with paprika money.
我会向他们提起你有多棒的
I'll mention how good you are to them.
不需要 他们知道的
No need, they already know.
对啊
That's right.
不分上下 难分胜负 不分呀宝贝呀 不分伯仲 难以置信 还难分胜负呢
Too close to call. Too close to call. It’s too close baby yeah. Too close to call. It’s unbelievable. It’s still too close to call
据我所知 想去嫖的雏儿都没现在这种纠结的情况
I've known sailors less likely to go either way than this.
抱歉... 说了黄段子
I... pardon my ribaldry.
- 伊利诺斯还是我们的 是吗?(20票) - 是的
- Hey, Illinois is still ours, isn't it? - Yes.
- 爱荷华州选择了O'Brien(4票) - 去他妈的爱荷华
- And lowa called for O'Brien. - Fuck lowa.
我想用核武器平了它 不过我觉得已经有人炸过了
I'd say nuke it, but I think someone already did.
宾夕法尼亚州难分胜负(20) 弗罗里达州势均力敌(29)
Pennsylvania's too close to call. Florida's too close to call.
你可以总结总体趋势
You might gather the general trend
就是势均力敌 难分胜负
is that it's too close to call.
国会的结果也一样势均力敌
The congressional results are similarly tight.
你不用摇那个袋子 好吗?
Okay, you don't need to shake that bag, all right?
试着闭上嘴嚼 看看行不行
Try chewing with your mouth closed. See if that works.
好了 他们说我们将在大约一小时后
All right, they're saying we're gonna get a clearer picture
对整体情况有更清楚的了解
of this whole thing in about an hour.
老天 我好紧张
God, I am so tense.
我的屁股都能夹碎核桃了
I could crack a walnut in my ass.
- 好了 妈 跟我来 - 什么?
- Right, Mom, come with me. - What?
等情况明了了再回来
Just get out of here until this picture becomes clearer.
- 来点亲子时间好吗? - 好吧
- Maybe have some mother-daughter time? - Okay.
Meyer-James 竞选集会, 巴尔的摩
请大家给群马乐队来点掌声
Everybody give it up for Band of the Horses.
等下 什么?
Wait, what?
哦 骏... 哦 抱歉
Oh, Band... Oh, I'm sorry.
抱歉 为骏马乐队鼓掌
I'm sorry. Give it up for Band of Horses.
骏马乐队
Band of Horses.
我想感谢你们
I just want to say thank you for supporting
对男性健康运动的支持
the men's health campaign
让我能够告诉男人们他们应该爱抚自己
and letting me tell guys that they should feel themselves up.
持续的变化
这是我做过的最简单的工作
Easiest job I ever had.
大家记得我的... 大家记得我的口号 对吗?
You guys remember my... you guys remember my catchphrase, right?
记得吗? 使劲想想
Remember it? Just to jog your memory.
要记得 经常检查 不要疏忽
Just remember, check'em, don't neglect 'em.
经常检查 不要疏忽
Check 'em, don't neglect 'em.
很好 大家记得A-Team (83年电视剧) 对吗?
Nice. You guys remember the A-Team, right?
A-Team? "我是A-Team"
A-Team? "I'm the A-Team."
T先生 嗯...
Mr. T. Um...
他们本该逃跑的
they were supposed to be on the run,
但是 你知道 他们在一个很特别的面包车里
but, you know, they were in a really distinctive van.
是啊 那是... 那是怎么回事?
Yeah, what was up... What was up with that?
感觉有点入禅的感觉 你知道吗?
Feeling kind of zen-ish, you know?
我意识到没有什么我能做的了
I realize that there's nothing more I can do.
事情已经脱离了我的控制
Things are out of my control
我必须抛弃紧张情绪
and I just have to let the tension go.
滚开 Kent
Get the fuck out of here, Kent.
抱歉
Apologies.
你和Jason 我很遗憾
I'm sorry about you and Jason.
我知道我的工作让你有些困难
I know that my job can be hard on you
这实在有点扫兴 是吗?
and that was a bit of a bummer, huh?
- 是的 有一点点 - 是的
- Yeah, just a little bit. - Yeah.
但是就像你说的 我不能和一个说客结婚 所以...
But like you said, I can't be married to a lobbyist, so...
是的 而且他得有60了吧
Yeah, and he was, like, 60.
- 他35 - 他接受的如何?
- He was 35. - How did he take it?
很难说 他感情不易波动
It's hard to tell. He's not really big on emotions.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
你知道吗 Catherine
You know, Catherine,
男人都糟透了
men are horrible.
好吗?
Okay?
我是说 我不得不
I mean, I have to just
这样告诉你 甜心
tell it to you like it is, honey.
所有男人都可恶极了
But all men are awful.
真的
Really.
重点只是找到一个
And the key is to just find a man
最不那么糟糕的男人
who's the least horrible.
好的 妈妈
Okay, Mom.
看 你和我的照片
Oh, look at that photo of you and me.
- 你在那张照片里很像我 - 不像
- You look like me in that picture. - No.
不像 一点不像
No, uh-uh. Not at all.
- 像 有一点... - 不像
- Yeah, a little bit... - No, uh-uh.
- 哦 - 哦 这是爸爸
- Oh. - Oh, there's Daddy.
- 糟透了 - 妈
- Horrible. - Mom.
好了 我回来了 我走了多久?
Okay, I'm back. How long was I gone?
- 大概20分钟 - 真的吗?
- About 20 minutes. - Is that it?
老天 和Catherine在一起时间总是感觉如此漫长
God, it always seems longer with Catherine.
好吧 我的命运如何了?
All right, so what's my destiny here?
仍然不可预测
Still unfathomable.
为什么美国人民如此优柔寡断?
Why can't the American people make up their minds?
我说 两个候选人选一个有多难?
I mean, how hard is it to decide between two candidates?
去他妈的
Oh, for fuck's sake.
- Amy - 嗨 Sue
- Amy. - Hey, Sue.
- Amy 很高兴见到你 - 你好
- Amy, nice to see you. - Hi. Mmm.
我得在Karen的嘴和我的耳朵之间找点空间
I've got to get a little space between Karen's mouth and my ears.
我要去买点汽水 大家要什么吗?
I'm gonna hit the soda machine. Anybody want anything?
放了真糖的东西
Just something with real sugar.
不要甜味剂 否则我就要拉裤子了(甜味剂吃多了腹泻)
No sweeteners or I'll shit my pants.
- 欢迎回来 - 谢谢
- Welcome back. - Thank you.
- 您好 夫人 - 哦 哇哦
- Hello, ma'am. - Oh, wow.
电视上的Amy Brookheimer
TV's Amy Brookheimer.
我感觉我应该在这里 夫人
I felt that I needed to be here, ma'am.
我们一起经历了那么多才让您走到这里 所以...
We went through so much together getting you here, so...
宾夕法尼亚的结果马上要出来了 他们正准备宣布
Pennsylvania results are about to come in. They're about to call this.
所以那个怎么... - 嘘
So how is it... - Shh.
宾夕法尼亚预测投给O'Brien(20票)
Pennsylvania called for O'Brien.
哦 不可能!
Oh, no way!
- 我早就说我们应该到那去拉票 - 你是对的
- I said we should have gone back there. - And you were right.
- 你当时为啥要辞职? - 很难说
- Why did you ever resign? - It's hard to understand.
我认为宾夕法尼亚州是今晚真正有着重大意义的投票
I think Pennsylvania is the real significant call tonight.
宾夕法尼亚 Matty 你认为Meyer会赢下它 对吗?
Pennsylvania, you had that as a Meyer win, is that right, Matty?
对 呃... 是的
Yeah, uh... yes.
这个 呃... 是这么认为的
That's, um... Yes, we did.
不能总是料事如神 是吧?
Can't predict everything all the time, can you?
尽管这是你的本职工作
Even though that is your job.
Dan 这是Meyer总统生涯的结束吗?
Is this the end for President Meyer, Dan?
如果总统这么快就考虑打给O'Brien议员认输
Well, I would not be surprised if the president were thinking
我不会感到惊讶的
about calling Senator O'Brien very soon to concede this election.
专家们知道个屁?
What do experts know?
O'Brien267票 我们207票
Got O'Brien 267, us 207.
如果这是真的 貌似他要赢下选举了
If those are right, it looks like he's got the election.
这些都只是预测 不是真正的结果
These are projections. These are not real results.
只是捕风捉影
They're ghosts.
你不能... 你不能认输
You can't... you can't concede.
我知道你想认输 但你真的 真的不应该这样
I know you want to, but you really, really shouldn't.
或者...
Or...
咋了?
What?
我要认输了
I'm gonna concede.
我 呃...
I, Uh...
我觉得这么拖下去没什么意义
I don't see any point in dragging this on.
我希望我输也要输的有尊严
And I'd like to have a little bit of dignity in defeat.
所以 呃...
So, um...
我要给O'Brien打电话
I'm gonna call O'Brien.
反正这傻逼工作也不咋地
This fucking job sucks anyway.
请千万别电死我
Please don't electrocute me.
接下来是总统和您讲话
The next voice you hear will be the president.
- Bill - 多美好的夜晚啊 夫人
- Bill. - A fascinating night, ma'am.
总统女士 给我打电话有什么特别原因吗?
Were you calling me for a particular reason, Madam President?
首先我要感谢你
I wanted to just start by thanking you
领导了一项庄重的...
for conducting a very dignified...
- Ben
- Ben.
是 Mike Selina在认输
Yeah, Mike, Selina's conceding,
所以 别弄汽水了 来箱威士忌
so forget about the soda and just grab a crate of whiskey.
妈的
Fuck.
- 我知道了
-  I know.
是时候把上吊绳变成领带了 哥们
Time to turn that noose back into a necktie, buddy.
我有你想听的消息
I got something you're gonna want to hear.
Dan 你告诉我的都没有屁用
Dan, there's nothing useful you can tell me.
宾夕法尼亚投票结果搞错了
Pennsylvania was the wrong call.
我们认为Selina要赢了
We think it's gonna go Selina.
听着 我不知道怎么...
Look, I have no idea how...
不! 不要! 不要！别认输!
No! Don't! Don't! Stop the concession!
所以 Bill 我觉得是时候该告诉你
So, Bill, I feel now is the time to call you
- 呃... - 女士 不要 不不不
- and... - Ma'am, don't. No, no, no.
呃 我还要说另一件事...
Um, also another thing I'd like to just mention...
呃 你过得怎么样?
Uh, how's it going?
过得怎么样?
How's it going?
只有咱俩
You and I are the only ones
经历着相同的事情
sort of going through the same thing
我只是...
and I just...
夫人 恕我直言
Ma'am, forgive me for being direct,
可你不是要认输的么?
but you're not conceding?
不 我不知道什么
Um, no. I don't know why
让你认为我要认输 Bill
you would even imagine that I would be doing that, Bill.
赢下宾夕法尼亚的是Selina
people of Pennsylvania go to Selina Meyer.
是啊 我不知道你看见了没 Bill
Yeah, I don't know if you've seen this, Bill,
不过他们好像宣布宾夕法尼亚投给我了
but they seem to have called Pennsylvania for me.
是 我听到了
Yes, I heard that.
我好奇你现在是不是
I wonder if there's anything that you
有什么想和我说的
would like to say to me right now.
我会入主白宫 把热澡盆给我准备好
I'm taking the White House. Please leave the hot tub on.
我不这么认为 亲爱的朋友
I don't think so, my friend.
凌晨 1：30
巴尔的摩Meyer James竞选集会
先生 人群越来越焦躁 乐队也停止演奏了
Sir, the crowd is getting restless. The band has stopped playing.
我已经黔驴技穷不知道怎么办了
I've given them my best material and we don't know what to do.
我们需要给他们来一剂政治兴奋剂
We need to give them a hit of political meth.
我觉得我们应该派Tom去
I think we should send out Tom James.
呃 女士 你介意让Tom去
Uh, ma'am, would you consider allowing Tom
竞选集会台上吗?
to go out on the rally stage?
什么? 呃 这个 我看看 首先 不行
What? Uh, well, let's see. First of all, no.
其次我还是非常想说的是
And then the other thing I really wanted to say
不行
was no.
我听见了个不行
I'm hearing a no.
Jonah 不好意思 答案是...
Jonah, sorry, the answer is...
哦 天噜
Oh, hello.
- 怎么了? - 我的个老天爷的七舅老爷
- What? - Holy mother of moly.
- 是怎么了? - 夫人 福克斯电视台宣布我们拿下华盛顿州了(12票)
- What is it? - Ma'am, Fox is calling Washington State for us.
好! - 不是吧!
Yes! - No!
- 拿下俄亥俄 - 哦 天噜 太棒啦!
- They called Ohio. - Oh, my God, that's amazing!
俄亥俄? - 不 是O'Brien拿下了 我该说清楚
Ohio? - No, for O'Brien. I should have said.
- 哦 天啊 - ABC电视台说这实在是势均力敌 难分高下
- Oh, my God. - ABC is saying it's still too close to call.
- 是啊 - 不 他们正在宣布...  O'Brien赢了
- Yeah. - No, they're calling it now... O'Brien.
- 妈蛋! - 还是福克斯还有政客新闻网
- Shit! - Fox again and Politico.
宣布新罕布什尔和俄亥俄投给O'Brien
New Hampshire to O'Brien and Ohio.
- 太好了 我们拿下了佛罗里达! - 哦!
- Yes, we took Florida! - Oh!
- 太牛逼了 - 是啊
- That is extraordinary. - Yes.
- Kent 我现在票数多少? - 好的 等一下
- What is my number now, Kent? - Okay, one second.
你是2.. 你是... - 多少?
You're two... You're... - What?
- 查到了 您的票数是256 - Kent 现在情况怎么样?
- Yeah, you're 256. - Kent, where does that leave us?
好的 现在就看弗吉尼亚州的选票了
Okay, it all comes down to Virginia.
如果O'Brien在弗吉尼亚州胜出  他就赢定了
If O'Brien gets Virginia, he wins.
- 但是 如果我们在弗吉尼亚州胜出... - 我们就赢定了!
- However, if we get Virginia... - We win!
不 其实  Gary 就算我们赢得了弗吉尼亚 我们也是正好打个平局
No, actually, Gary, if we get it, we tie.
- 啥? - 什么啥?
- What? - What?
虽然我没目不转睛的盯着选票数据
I don't follow these things that closely,
但就是这样 对吧 Davison先生?
but that's right, isn't it, Mr. Davison?
是的
Yes.
平局 居然是平局? 你确定 我们是平局?
Tie, like it's a tie? You mean, we tie?
- 确实是  - Greg 但最出人意料的  是这件事的影响
- You do. - The real shock, Greg, is where this leaves us.
如果总统夫人拿下弗吉尼亚州 两位候选人就是齐头并进
Neck and neck if the president takes Virginia.
Matty 不好意思这次我要略过你了
Matty, you'll forgive me if I sideline you here.
- 没问题- Dan 你了解总统
- Sure. - Dan, you know the president well.
此时此刻 Meyer酒店套间里的人到底在干嘛呢?
What is going on in that Meyer hotel suite right this second?
总统的智囊团有很多专家在为选举奔波
The president has a lot of top minds working on her campaign.
他们现在肯定全在忙活这事
They're gonna be all over this.
如果打成平局会怎么样?
What happens when there's a tie?
所有人都在上网
Everybody goes online to
搜索 想搞明白我们平局后该怎么办
try to find out what happens if we get a tie.
我动作比你快多了 靠 我搜的是如何打领带(tie同有平局和领带意思)
Way ahead of you. Shit, I'm just getting how to tie a tie.
有相关的书吗?  就那种老式的... 纸质的书?
Is there a book? Like an old-fashioned... like a paper book?
我的天呐 知道吗?
Jesus Christ, you know?
就算你竭尽全力 想为人民服务
You do your best. You try to serve the people
- 可是那些人人却把你操个人仰马翻 - 是啊
- and then they just fuck you over. - Yeah.
你知道这是为什么? 因为他们愚昧无知
And you know why? Because they're ignorant
他们蠢到粪坑里
and they're dumb as shit.
而女士们先生们 这 就是民主
And that, ladies and gentlemen, is democracy.
- 该死的玩意儿 - 第十二修正案
- God damn it. - It's the 12th Amendment.
- 我查到第二十修正案 - 怎么这么多修正案?
- I have 20th Amendment. - Why are there so many amendments?
一次性搞清楚行么  同志们
Get it right the first time, people.
其实两个都对  第十二修正案被第二十修正案取代了
It's actually both. 12th is superseded by the 20th.
他们允许白宫在一月二十日之前进行总统选举
They give the House until January 20th to elect the president.
每个州一张选票
Each state gets one vote.
第一个得到26张选票的候选人即为新总统
First candidate to 26 is the new president
然后由参议院选出副总统
and the Senate chooses the VP.
这种选举难分胜负
It's a close election
很多众议院都难分胜负势均力敌
with a ton of House races too close to call.
如果众议院选举结果还是平局呢?
What happens if it's a tie in the House?
对啊   - 跳舞决胜负吗?
Right. - Is it a dance-off?
这样的话 副总统候选人将会成为总统
Well, vice president-elect becomes president.
参议院选谁做副总统 谁就能当总统
Whoever the Senate has picked for VP will be president.
- 等等  这样的话...   - 那Tom...
- Wait, that means... - That Tom...
什么? - 可能会成为总统
What? - Could be the president.
呃 我...
Well, I...
我还不清楚这是怎么回事
I had literally no idea.
不过做好准备总没错
It's good to be prepared.
这样 等等 你的意思是我...
So, wait. So you mean that I...
我他妈的要输给我他娘自己的副总统?
I might lose this election to my fucking vice president?
至少总统是从我们团队出来的 夫人
At least it'd be somebody from our team, ma'am.
我是说 这也是好事 对吧?
I mean, that's good, right?
我可没想惹她哭
I didn't mean to make her cry.
- 没事 没事
- There, there.
哦 一切都会好的
Oh, it's gonna be okay.
- 她要倒下了  - 她要倒下了
- She's going down. - She's going down.
别碰她
Don't touch her.
- 喂?   - 先生 很抱歉直接联系您
- Yeah? - Sir, I'm sorry to contact you directly,
但是现场的人们个个垂涎欲滴的样子要见您
but the crowd is drooling for you.
是啊 地板都被口水弄湿了
Yep, floor is wet out here.
- 好的 太好了 谢谢 - Tom James! Tom James!
- Okay, great. Thank you. - Tom James! Tom James!
我去会场振奋一下士气
I'm gonna go rally the rally.
恕我直言
With all due respect,
你现在必须振作起来 女士
you need to get your shit together now, lady.
硬气点 你还是这个自由国度的元首
Ma'am up. You're still the leader of the free world.
嗯?
Hmm?
Tom去哪了?
Where's Tom?
噢  他去会场为大家讲话去了
Oh, he's gone to talk to the crowd at the rally.
- 什么? - 他妈的他想干什么
- What? - The fuck he has.
你怎么能允许他这么干?
Why would you let him do that?
- 哦 你又不在这工作  - 你也不属于这
- Well, you don't work here. - Well, neither do you.
好好 去他妈的 我要去会场
All right, fuck all of you. I'm going to the rally.
夫人 夫人  这史无前例
Ma'am, ma'am, that would be unprecedented.
没有 我告诉你什么叫史无前例 Kent
No, I'll tell you what's unprecedented, Kent.
平局是史无前例
A tie is unprecedented.
成为首位女性总统也是史无前例
So is becoming the first lady president.
那个想走捷径当总统的王八蛋也是史无前例
So is that jackoff becoming president through the back door.
知道了吧? 现在已经没有规则了
Okay? The rule book's been torn up now
这个国家已经把一切规则都擦了屁股了
and America is wiping its nasty ass with it.
别他妈挡着我!
Get the fuck out of my way!
- 夫人! 夫人!  - 我们走
- Ma'am! Ma'am! - Let's go.
Tom James! Tom James!
Tom James!
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧 我承认 这有点意思
Okay, I admit, this isn't boring.
为什么总选票数会一模一样?
Why make the total of electoral votes an even number?
- 神经错乱? - 我知道 今夜很漫长
- Insanity? - Listen, I know this is a long night.
你们又冷又累 腿都站疼了
You're tired and you're cold and your legs ache
还很想去洗手间
and you need the bathroom.
哎呀 你们肯定内急得很了
Boy, you need the bathroom.
那个混蛋
That fucking guy
他假惺惺的魅力  他的混蛋儿子
with his fucking charm and his fucking son
他的烂轮椅还有他的脊椎  都死去吧
and his fucking wheelchair with his spine all fucked up.
我奶奶从黑色风暴事件中活了下来
My grandmother survived the Dust Bowl.
而在她89岁时去世前
And before she died at the age of 89,
曾告诉我一个她保守了近50年的秘密
she told me a secret that she kept for almost 50 years.
故事是说...
The story concerns...
女士们 先生们 Tom James
Ladies and gentlemen, Tom James.
大家好不好?
How about it?
谢谢大家 谢谢大家
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢你们 哇
Thank you. Wow.
我知道怎么接话茬吗? 当然知道了
Do I know how to pick 'em? Yep.
很感谢你们来到这里
Well, thank you so much for being here.
我知道你们等了很久
I know it's been a wait.
而且我们真的很感谢你们的到来
And we really do appreciate your presence.
真是一个难忘的晚上 对不对?
What a night, right?
是万里挑一的难忘夜晚
It's the night of nights.
呃 你们知道我想做什么吗?
Um, you know what I want to do?
我想把你们介绍给
I want to introduce you to the First Daughter
美国的第一女儿
of the United States,
我的女儿Catherine Selina Meyer
my daughter Catherine Selina Meyer.
Catherine
很高兴...
Always a delight to have...
她是个漂亮的姑娘 我为她感到十分骄傲
She is such a beautiful girl. I'm so proud of her.
在我们准备揭示弗吉尼亚州投票之前
Well, we have another minute
我们还有一分钟左右的时间
or so before we're prepared to call Virginia.
就看看一些选区的状况吧
Just checking a couple of precincts.
我们今晚做了几次不成熟的预测
We've made some premature calls this evening.
那么我们现在都极其想知道这次的最终结果
So we're anxious to be absolutely certain this time.
不如我们来见一见那些
Why don't we meet some of the people
帮助我竞选的人员吧?
who lift me up?
我想让大家见见他们
I'd like you to meet them.
同志们 出来吧 这些伟大的面孔如何?
Guys, come on out. How about these great faces?
惊人的一幕 史无前例
Incredible scenes. Never happened before.
非常感人的时刻 Dan 你也希望在那里吧?
Very emotional moment. Dan, do you wish you were there?
我确信在那里是件令人激动的事
I'm sure it's a very exciting place to be at.
从来没有过像这次一样的选举
There's never been an election like this.
没有
No.
你肯定想在那儿
You must want to be there.
乡亲们 你们不认识她 但这是Karen Collins
Folks, you don't know her, but this is Karen Collins.
我们成为朋友也有一段时间了
And she has been a friend of mine for a while.
是的
Yep.
这位是Amy Brookheimer
And Amy Brookheimer is here.
Amy Brookheimer非常成功地组织了我的竞选活动
Amy Brookheimer who so successfully ran my campaign
直到她生病不适为止
until she became unwell.
我还想像大家介绍一位今晚不在场
I'll tell you somebody else that is not here tonight
但有参与到我们竞选团队的人...
who was with the campaign...
Dan 看样子是说你哦
Sounds like it could be you, Dan.
好吧 那我会超级感动的
Well, I would be incredibly touched.
毫无疑问 这个人就是Leslie Kerr
And that is, of course, Leslie Kerr.
我相信Lesile也会感谢各位
I'm sure Leslie is thanking you, too.
我听到现在可以预测弗吉尼亚州的投票结果了
And I'm hearing we can now project a Virginia result.
- Dan 预测结果如何? -谢谢 Greg
- Dan, what is that projection? - Thank you, Greg.
CNN准备做以下预测
CNN is prepared to make the following projection
这13张选举人票
that Virginia, with its 13 electoral votes,
被Meyer总统赢得了
is a win for President Meyer.
选举打平了
This election is a tie.
我们做到了!
We did it!
我们还有一个障碍要跨过
We have one more hurdle to overcome.
而且我们会跨过的
And we shall overcome.
我们还有一条河流要穿过
One more river to cross.
还有一座山要攀爬
One more mountain to climb.
但我已经在山顶上了
But I have been to the mountaintop.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
感谢所有制作人员(排名不分先后)
翻译
埃可博
坑坑
大妖怪
惊鸣
libear
旁白
糖佩斯
rebecca
鑫鑫美少女
凯莉
柯迪夫
紫苑
凯莉
泡泡
圆滚滚
五娃会吐水
言之
校对
Xz
天然绯
埃可博
霉霉
拉拉
时间轴 & 特效
圈圈
柯迪夫
惊鸣
火山
嵬森
double
压制
太阳雨
天天
- 我不知道要做什么 - 我们什么都不做
- I don't know what to do. - We don't do anything.
- 你做你该做的事情 - 对 我该一醉方休
- You do what you have to do. - Yeah, I'm getting drunk.
嘿 Dan 你收到这条信息时
Hey, Dan, when you get this,
能帮我在Greg面前美言几句吗?
can you put in a good word for me with Greg?
我觉得我需要保住在电视台的工作
I think that I need to keep my TV work going.
听着 你一定会赢 你要是不赢 我就自杀
Okay, you're gonna win. And if you don't, I'll kill myself.
Kent 下一步怎么走? 你要知道的
Kent, what happens next? You've got to know.
不 我恐怕不知道 一些议院的选举还在变
No, I'm afraid not. Some of these House races,
- 它们还是势均力敌 难分高下 - 这是什么意思?
- they're still too close to call. - What does that mean?
就是 现在我们还不能预测最终
Well, presently, we cannot predict the result
1月20日国会的投票结果
of the vote in Congress on January 20.
- 我们算是在炼狱的困境之中 - 欢迎来到我的世界
- We're in a kind of purgatory. - Welcome to my world.
你就不能一秒钟都不想
Can you stop thinking
- 你自己吗? - 老实说
- about yourself for one second? - Honestly.
不能 因为我要进监狱了 我有说过这点吧?
No, because I'm going to prison. Have I mentioned that?
- 那我们现在该干什么? - 我们要放气球吗?
- So what are we gonna do here? - Should we drop the balloons?
- 不 不要气球了 - 或者放下一半?
- No, no balloons. - Maybe just drop half of them?
- 不要! - 我们为什么要有这些气球?
- No! - Why do we even have balloons?
夫人 我到台上讲话
Ma'am, I seriously overstepped the mark
是严重的僭越 那简直就是愚不可及 一团糟
going out onstage. That was a fuck-up.
是 我觉得
Yeah, I'll say.
你要是成了总统会想回头看这一段的
You might want to watch that if you become president.
如果真发生了
If that does happen,
你愿意做我的副总统吗?
want to be my veep?
你为什么不去帮他们弄弄气球?
Why don't you go help them with the balloons?
收到
Copy that.